Isaiah (Ike) Bloyer

Pembroke Pines, FL | (954) 684-9766 | isaiah@bloyer.net

SUMMARY

Experienced technical support specialist with 4 years of experience working at Apple. Hold a Bachelor's of Science in Information Technology and a Minor in Secure Computing and Networks from the University of Central Florida. Results based individual seeking full-time employment in software, networking, or hardware fields

EDUCATION

University of Central Florida

Orlando, FL

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Aug 2018 - Dec 2023

Minor in Secure Computing and Networks

Relevant Coursework: Programming, Networking, Security, Cryptology, Hardware Architecture

WORK EXPERIENCE

Apple Orlando, FL

AppleCare Mac+ Advisor

Feb 2020 - Jan 2024

- Technical support for multiple Apple hardware, software, and service related issues
- Demonstrated excellent customer service skills and maintained a high customer satisfaction rating
- Experience with large and multifaceted public and private resources
- Consistently upgrading and updating knowledge and training bases on rapid changes at Apple

Apple Seed Reader

June 2023 - July 2023

- iOS and MacOS public beta feedback reader
- Technical writing to assist with new feature support and bug reports
- Collaboration with various internal organizations to work towards issue resolution

SKILLS

- Strong problem-solving
- Excellent verbal and written communication
- Ability to multitask and prioritize tasks effectively
- Self-sufficient work ethic and ability to work within a large team environment
- Familiarity working at a global scale
- Experience with Java, JavaScript, NodeJS, C, SQL, HTML, Windows, MacOS, Unix/Linux, iOS, Docker

CERTIFICATIONS

- ISC2 Cybersecurity Certification (In-Progress)
- Apple Certified Mac Technician
- Apple Certified iOS Technician
- AutoCad Certification

ADDITIONAL

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/isaiah-bloyer **GitHub:** github.com/IsaiahBloyer

Website: isaiah.bloyer.net

Awards: AppleCare Excellence Award Winner Summer 2022

References: Available upon request